报告，契科夫先生
Report, Mr. Chekov.
全面扫描，结果阴性
Full scan. Results negative.
辐射水平正常
Radiation level normal.
大气和地形不受干扰，没有证据表明有殖民地
Atmosphere and terrain are undisturbed. No evidence of a colony
也没有可能消灭它的军队
nor of a force that might have annihilated it.
- 生命读数，麦考伊医生  - 没有
- Life readings, Dr. McCoy. - Nothing.
- 他们被一艘船袭击了  - 我们无法检测到
- They were being attacked by a ship. - Which we were unable to detect.
一整个人类殖民地
An entire human colony,
一整个定居点
a whole settlement,
100名男性、女性和儿童
100 men, women and children.
谁干的？
Who did it?
为什么？
And why?
[通讯器发出哔哔声]
[COMMUNICATOR BLEEPS]
- 我是柯克  - 史波克，舰长
- Kirk here. - Spock, Captain.
传感器发现了一艘克林贡船，正在快速接近
Sensors have picked up a Klingon ship, closing fast.
开启护盾，保护自己
Deflectors on. Protect yourselves.
如果受到攻击，全面反击
Total reply if attacked.
这就是答案，克林贡人
So that's the answer. Klingons.
克林贡船上有麻烦，有爆炸的迹象，大规模的破坏
Trouble on the Klingon ship. Evidence of explosions, massive destruction.
舰长，敌舰正在漂流，完全失去战斗力
Captain, the enemy ship is drifting, totally disabled.
- 我们从未向它开过枪  - 维持红色警报
- We never fired upon it. - Maintain Red Alert.
克林贡：你袭击了我的船
KLINGON: You attacked my ship.
我的400名船员死亡
400 of my crew dead.
柯克，我的飞船已瘫痪，我要你的
Kirk, my ship is disabled. I claim yours.
你们是克林贡帝国的俘虏
You are prisoners of the Klingon Empire
你们对它们犯下了战争行为
against which you have committed an act of war.
柯克：宇宙，最后的边疆
KIRK: Space, the final frontier.
这些是星舰企业号的航程
These are the voyages of the starship Enterprise.
它的五年任务：探索未知的新世界
Its five-year mission: To explore strange new worlds,
寻找新生命和新文明
to seek out new life and new civilizations,
勇踏前人未至之境
to boldly go where no man has gone before.
三年来，联邦和克林贡帝国
For three years, the Federation and the Klingon Empire
一直很和平
have been at peace.
- 我们遵守条约  - 我们没有对你的飞船采取任何行动
- A treaty we have honored. - We took no action against your ship.
我的船员的尖叫声是假的吗？
Were the screams of my crew imaginary?
你的命令是什么？发动战争？你成功了
What were your orders? To start a war? You've succeeded.
测试新武器？我们将对其进行调查
To test a new weapon? We shall examine it.
- 这个星球上的一个殖民地被摧毁了  - 通过什么方式？
- A colony on this planet was destroyed. - By what?
没有尸体，没有废墟，隐形的殖民地？
No bodies, no ruins. A colony of the invisible?
是的，克林贡新武器的测试，不留痕迹
Yes, the test of a new Klingon weapon, leaving no traces.
联邦舰艇不擅长偷袭
Federation ships don't specialize in sneak attacks.
我们想知道你什么时候开始
We wondered when you would begin.
你用虚假的求救信号引诱我的船进入伏击
You lured my ship into ambush by a false distress call.
你会告诉我们为什么
You will tell us why.
你也接到了？我们也接到了求救信号
You received one? We received a distress call.
我不打算用我的余生来争论你的幻想
I don't propose to spend the rest of my life arguing your fantasies.
企业号是我的！
The Enterprise is mine!
指示您的传送室将我们传送到上船
Instruct your transporter room to beam us aboard.
见鬼去吧
Go to the Devil.
我们没有鬼，柯克
We have no Devil, Kirk.
但我们了解你们的魔鬼的习惯
But we understand the habits of yours.
我要折磨你们…至死
I shall torture you... to death,
一个接一个
one by one,
直到你们高贵的舰长喊“够了”
until your noble captain cries "Enough".
谁会是第一个？
Who will be first?
哥萨克！
Cossacks!
肮脏的克林贡杀人犯！
Filthy Klingon murderers!
你杀了我的兄弟，皮奥特！阿卡尼斯四号研究前哨站
You killed my brother, Piotre! The Archanis IV research outpost.
100名和平人士被屠杀！就像你在这里所做的一样
100 peaceful people massacred! Just like you did here.
我的兄弟…
My brother...
你自愿加入他，真是忠诚啊
And you volunteer to join him. That is loyalty.
契科夫！
Chekov!
停止折磨
Stop the torture.
- 你不能交出企业号  - 帮助契科夫
- You can't hand over the Enterprise. - Help Chekov.
不要计划任何诡计，柯克
Don't plan any tricks, Kirk.
一有背叛迹象我就杀死100名人质
I will kill 100 hostages at the first sign of treachery.
我会让你登上企业号，一旦到了那里，就没有花招了
I'll beam you aboard the Enterprise. Once there, no tricks.
舰长，你不能，不要让这些畜生占有这艘船
Captain, you can't. Don't let these animals have the ship.
- 让开  - 畜生？
- Move aside. - Animals?
你的舰长爬得像个畜生
Your captain crawls like one.
克林贡人永远不会投降
A Klingon would never surrender.
命令传送所有人上去
Order everybody to be transported up.
对准他所有武器
All weapons on him.
- 柯克呼叫企业号，史波克先生  - 我在，舰长
- Kirk to Enterprise. Mr. Spock. - Here, Captain.
史波克先生，我们有客人，将传送机调整到宽阔的场地
Mr. Spock, we have guests. Adjust transporter to wide field.
传送目标区域内的所有人
Beam up everyone in the target area.
收到，舰长
Understood, Captain.
传送室
Transporter room.
警卫，立刻来，干得好，史波克
Security, on the double. Good work, Spock.
- 发生了什么？  - 我们的小队完好无损
- What happened? - Our party is intact.
其他人在传送中暂停，他们是谁？
All others suspended in transit. Who are they?
- 克林贡人  - 好了，他们到了
- Klingons. - Well, they're right in here.
- 约翰逊？  - 警卫在路上
- Johnson? - Security on the way.
把它们留在原地，不存在的地方
Leave them where they are, non-existence.
这样银河系中的克林贡怪物就少了
That's less Klingon monsters in the galaxy.
带他们进来
Bring them in.
快走，快走
Move 'em out. Move.
说谎者！
Liar!
我说我们上船后不玩把戏
I said no tricks after we reach the ship.
你是星际联邦的囚犯
You're a prisoner of the Federation of Planets.
我的船上有幸存者
There are survivors on my ship.
我无法接通星际舰队司令部
I can't get through to Starfleet Command.
所有频率都被拦截
All frequencies are blocked.
那艘克林贡船的辐射太多了
There's too much radiation from that Klingon ship.
- 这是一个风险  - 准备摧毁
- It's a hazard. - Prepare to destruct.
完成你开始的工作？
Completing the job you started?
- 如果是我干的，你就不会在这里  - 来自克林贡飞船的第一组
- You wouldn't be here if I had. - First group from the Klingon vessel.
我的妻子玛拉和我的科学官
My wife, Mara, and my science officer.
- 康，发生了什么事？  - 更多的联邦背叛
- Kang, what has happened? - More Federation treachery.
我们是囚犯
We are prisoners.
他们会对我们做什么？
What will they do to us?
我听说过他们的暴行，死亡集中营
I've heard of their atrocities, death camps.
他们会折磨我们套取信息
They'll torture us for information.
你有东西要学， 为我们的客人编写食物合成器的程序
You have things to learn. Program the food synthesiser for our guests.
- 你会得到很好的待遇  - 我看到了
- You'll be well treated. - So I have seen.
维持红色警报
Secure from Red Alert.
保持战斗部署，扫描其他船只
Maintain general quarters. Scan for other ships.
- 我想搞清楚这件事  - 我们知道发生了什么
- I want this nailed down. - We know what happened.
在我们收到贝塔12A信号的那一刻
At the moment we received the signal from Beta 12A,
克林贡人距离太远，不可能成为攻击者
the Klingons were too far distant to have been the attackers.
而且，他们也被求救信号所吸引
Moreover, they also were attracted by a distress call.
谎言！他们想假装我们发动战争
Lies! They want to start a war by pretending we did.
契科夫可能是对的
Chekov may be right.
克林贡人声称遵守停火协议，但发生的暴力事件…
The Klingons claim to honor the truce but there are incidents...
- 没有证据是克林贡人做的  - 我们需要什么证明？
- No proof Klingons committed them. - What proof do we need?
我们知道克林贡人是怎样的
We know what a Klingon is.
我们的日志磁带将表明我们的清白
Our log tapes will indicate our innocence.
不幸的是，不能保证他们会被相信
Unfortunately, there's no guarantee they'll be believed.
报告
Report.
仍然联系不上星际舰队司令部，长官
Still no contact with Starfleet Command, sir.
继续尝试，我们的捉到了一条外交大鱼的尾巴
Keep trying. We've got a diplomatic tiger by the tail.
- 斯科特：克林贡飞船已经撤离  - 非常好，苏鲁先生？
- SCOTT: Klingon ship has vacated. - Very good. Mr. Sulu?
- 相位炮锁定，准备开火  - 发射相位炮
- Phasers locked, ready to fire. - Fire phasers.
射程内没有其他飞船
No other ships within range.
- 上尉？  - 未能与星际舰队联系
- Lieutenant? - No contact with Starfleet yet.
改变航线为17，标记4，曲速3
Change course to 17, mark 4, warp factor 3.
当我拿下这艘船时，我会把柯克的头塞满挂在墙上
When I take this ship, I'll have Kirk's head stuffed and hung on the wall.
他们会在我们采取行动之前杀死我们
They will kill us before we can act.
他们想要审问我们，了解我们的实力，我们的计划
They wish to question us, learn our strength, our plans.
- 他们永远不会得逞  - 我们40人对他们400人
- They never will. - We are 40 against 400.
一个奔走的人一夜间可以割断4000人的喉咙
4,000 throats may be cut in one night by a running man.
耐心，警觉
Patience, vigilance.
他们会犯错的
They will make their mistake.
企业号将为我们提供快速结束这场战争的知识
The Enterprise will give us knowledge to end this war quickly.
舰长！
Captain!
这说不通，载波正常，仍然没有外部联系
This doesn't make sense. Carriers normal. Still no outside contact.
我不明白
I don't understand.
会是克林贡人在捣鬼吗？
Could the Klingons be doing something?
[碰撞]
[CRASH]
- 苏鲁？  - 改变航线，加速
- Sulu? - Change of course. Accelerating.
船舵失灵，辅助导航失灵
Helm dead. Auxiliary navigation dead.
手动控制
Override.
没有任何反应，舰长
Nothing responds, Captain.
- 斯科提，停止所有引擎  - 我不能
- Scotty, stop all engines. - I can't.
控制器已经疯了，有些东西被接管了
The controls have gone crazy. Something's taken over.
- 斯科提！  - 引擎已经到曲速9了…
- Scotty! - The engines have gone to warp 9...
…靠自己！
...by themselves!
新航线？
New course?
- 苏鲁：902，标记5  - 这将带我们离开银河系
- SULU: 902, mark 5. - That'll take us out of the galaxy.
舰长
Captain.
来自下层甲板的报告，应急舱壁已关闭
Reports from the lower decks. Emergency bulkheads have closed.
大约400名船员被困在那里
Almost 400 crewmen are trapped down there.
真有趣
Most interesting.
你的大部分船员被困了
The bulk of your crew trapped.
你的飞船不受控制地飞出这个星系
Your ship racing from this galaxy at wild speeds.
有意思，我怎么能进行这种破坏的？我所有的人都在这里
Delightful. How did I perform this sabotage? All my men are here.
约翰逊，去警卫部，搜索每个区域
Johnson. Get down to security. Search every section.
克林贡人可能已经在未被发现的情况下传送上船了
Klingons may have beamed aboard undetected.
去轮机部帮助斯科提解救那些被困船员
Get down to engineering and help Scotty free those trapped crewmen.
在我把你关禁闭前，我欠你一些东西
Before I put you in the brig, there's something I owe you.
相位枪
Phasers.
站起来战斗吧，你们这些懦夫
Stand and fight, you cowards.
医务室
Sickbay.
舰桥
Bridge.
克林贡人逃脱了，他们会试图夺回这艘船
The Klingons are free. They'll try to take the ship.
- 我们有多少人？  - 392人被困在下面
- How many men do we have? - 392 trapped below.
部署部队以保护辅助控制
Deploy forces to protect auxiliary control.
检查军械库，尝试释放船员
Check the armory. Try and free the crewmen.
门和隔板不会移动
The doors and bulkheads won't budge.
把它们炸开，我们需要人手
Blow them out. We need numbers.
- 你能控制船的速度吗？  - 她就是个曲速9的导弹
- Can you control the ship's speed? - She's a projectile, at warp 9.
- 不要问她为什么还没散架  - 通话完毕
- Don't ask what's holding her together. - Kirk out.
全面传感器扫描，报告克林贡人的任何动向
Full sensor scan. Report on any movement by the Klingons.
克林贡人有决斗的传统，希望用剑打败我们
The Klingons have a duelling tradition and hope to beat us with swords.
克林贡技术和我们的技术都无法做到这一点
Neither the Klingon technology, nor ours, is capable of this.
物质的瞬间转化，我怀疑他们是否有责任
Instantaneous transmutation of matter. I doubt they're responsible.
还有其他合乎逻辑的候选人吗？
Any other logical candidate?
没有，不过，如果他们有这样的实力
None. However, if they had such power,
他们不会创造出更有效的武器吗？
wouldn't they have created more effective weapons?
并且只为自己？
And only for themselves?
苏鲁先生，下来，接管轮机部和辅助控制
Mr. Sulu, get below. Take command of engineering and auxiliary control.
- 舰长  - 契科夫先生？
- Captain. - Mr. Chekov?
- 舰长！  - 和你一样
- Captain! - As you were.
- 契科夫！  - 长官
- Chekov! - Sir.
让我也去，我有个人恩怨要与克林贡人解决
Let me go too. I've a personal score to settle with the Klingons.
现在不是复仇的时候
This is no time for a vendetta.
- 舰长！  - 坚守你的岗位！
- Captain! - Maintain your post!
不要试图阻止我，舰长
Don't try to stop me, Captain.
我看到了皮奥特留下的东西
I saw what they left of Piotre.
我在他的坟前发誓我会为他的谋杀报仇
I swore on his grave I would avenge his murder.
契科夫和克林贡人有什么恩怨？谁是皮奥特？
What's Chekov's grudge against the Klingons? Who's Piotre?
他唯一的兄弟，在克林贡袭击中丧生
His only brother, killed in a Klingon raid.
他的兄弟？
His brother?
他从来没有过兄弟，他是独生子
He never had a brother. He's an only child.
- 着手轮机部的工作  - 是的，长官
- Get down to engineering. - Aye, sir.
警卫，我是舰长，找到契科夫先生并将他带去舰桥
Security, this is the captain. Find Mr. Chekov and bring him to the bridge.
舰长，为什么…为什么契科夫会相信他有一个兄弟？
Captain, why would... Why would Chekov believe he has a brother?
我不知道
I don't know.
但他知道
But he does.
现在，他要为一个不存在的损失报仇
And now, he wants revenge for a non-existent loss.
那里
There.
那些肮脏的屠夫
Those filthy butchers.
即使在战争中也有原则，不攻击一个倒下的人
There are rules, even in war. You don't hack at a man after he's down.
把那个努曼诺胶囊递给我
Hand me that numanol capsule.
企业号的布局和规格
Layout and specifications of the Enterprise.
敌人数量和我们一样
Enemy numbers are the same as ours.
- 战斗平衡  - 那我们就拿下这艘船
- A fighting balance. - Then we take this ship.
- 前往银河系的尽头？  - 尽快
- Heading to the end of the galaxy? - In time.
我们必须尽快拿下这些区域，首先，轮机部
We must take these sections. First, engineering.
- 我是柯克  - 我是斯科特，长官
- Kirk here. - Scott here, sir.
试图释放那些人是没有用的
There's no use trying to free those men.
移相器火炬不能切开舱壁
The phaser torches won't cut through the bulkheads,
门或甲板，金属有问题
the doors or decks. Something's happened to the metal.
- 军械库？  - 我正在这
- The armory? - I'm there now.
我一生中从未见过这样的古董收藏
You never saw such a collection of antiques in your life.
回到轮机部，尝试重新建立引擎控制
Get back to engineering, try and re-establish engine control.
与军械部讨论相位枪的更换的问题
Talk to ordnance about phaser replacements.
是的，长官
Aye, sir.
一把斩剑！
A claymore!
你是个尤物！
You're a beauty!
火光是怎么回事？
What the blazes is going on?
扫描表明我们的部队和克林贡人的部队
Scans indicate that our forces and those of the Klingons
完全相等，每边各38人
are exactly equal at 38 each.
克林贡控制甲板6和右舷甲板7
The Klingons control deck 6 and starboard deck 7
而我们控制上面的所有部分
while we control all sections above.
- 持续监视  - 真奇怪
- Constant surveillance. - Most curious.
船上有更多的生命能量单位
There are more life energy units on board
比船员和克林贡人加起来还多
than can be accounted for by the crew plus the Klingons.
- 有相当大的差异  - 更多的克林贡人在船上？
- A considerable discrepancy. - More Klingons beamed aboard?
我将尝试对克林贡单位进行补偿读取
I shall attempt a compensatory reading of Klingon units.
有那些恶魔的迹象吗？
Any signs of those devils?
一切都清楚了，斯科特先生
All clear, Mr. Scott.
他们拿下了轮机部
They've taken engineering.
我们分头行动，设法返回舰桥
We'll split up and try to make it back to the bridge.
全体：胜利！
ALL: Victory!
胜利！
Victory!
未检测到其他克林贡人
No additional Klingons detected.
它是一种外星生命力，一个单一的实体
It is an alien life force, a single entity.
我无法确定它的位置
I cannot ascertain its location.
外星生命力
An alien life force.
我们必须进行联系，找出它想要什么
We must make contact, find out what it wants.
读数转移到图书馆计算机进行分析
Readings diverted to library computer for analysis.
电脑报告
Computer report.
外星生命力由纯能量组成，类型未知
Alien life force is composed of pure energy, type unknown.
- 行为表现出智慧，目的  - 什么目的？
- Actions show intelligence, purpose. - What purpose?
数据不足，无法进一步分析
Insufficient data for further analysis.
一个不存在的兄弟，一个幻影殖民地
A brother that never existed, a phantom colony,
假的求救信号，这些武器的创造
imaginary distress calls, the creation of these weapons.
斯波克先生，你看到规律了吗？
Do you sense a pattern, Mr. Spock?
如果外星人正在创造这些事件
If the alien is creating these events,
它显然能够操纵物质和思想
it is apparently capable of manipulating matter and mind.
它控制着企业号，将我们带出银河系
It has control of the Enterprise, taking us out of the galaxy.
- 为什么？  - 我不得不指出
- Why? - I'm constrained to point out,
因为思维正在受到影响
that since minds are being influenced,
我们无法知道我们自己的记忆是否准确和真实
we cannot know whether our own memories are accurate and true.
我们必须和康谈谈
We must talk to Kang.
- 停战  - 适当的术语
- Bury the hatchet. - An appropriate term.
但很难与克林贡人停战
But it is difficult to arrange a truce with the Klingons
一旦流血开始
once blood has been drawn.
停战？你是认真的吗？
A truce? Are you serious?
医务室里有些人正在死去，他们的身上发生了暴行
I've got men in Sickbay, some dying, atrocities committed on their persons.
你说要与这些恶魔和解？
And you talk about making peace with these fiends?
他们马上就会扑向我们
They'd jump us in a minute,
你知道克林贡人是怎么对待囚犯的
and you know what Klingons do to prisoners.
- 奴役，死亡星球，实验！  - 麦考伊？
- Slavery, death planets, experiments! - McCoy?
你在滔滔不绝，他们在计划攻击，这是一场生死搏斗
You talk, they plan attacks. This is a fight to the death.
- 我们最好努力赢得它！  - 我们正试图结束它
- We'd better try to win it! - We are attempting to end it.
有更好的理由，船上的外星人可能造成了这种情况。
By reason, preferably. An alien on board may have created the situation.
谁在乎是什么开始的？我们被卷入了
Who cares what started it? We're in it!
杀人犯！我们应该消灭他们！
Murderers! We should wipe them out!
外星人才是真正的威胁，是我们必须消灭的敌人
The alien is the real threat, the enemy we must wipe out.
医务室呼叫，更多伤员需要你的关注
Sickbay calling. More wounded men require your attention.
在你表现得像军人而不是傻瓜之前，还要死多少人？
How many more must die before you act like military men instead of fools?
[通讯器发出哔哔声]
[COMMUNICATOR BLEEPS]
我是柯克
Kirk here.
- 我是康  - 有件事我们必须讨论
- This is Kang. - There's something we must discuss.
我占领了你的轮机部
I captured your engineering section.
我现在控制着这艘船的动力和生命支持系统
I now control the ship's power and life-support.
我已经切断了除我们以外所有区域的生命支持系统
I have deprived all areas except our own.
你会窒息而死
You will die of suffocation
在冰冷的太空中
in the icy cold of space.
企业号正驶出我们的银河系
The Enterprise is heading out of our galaxy,
由船上某处的神秘外星人控制
controlled by a mysterious alien somewhere aboard the ship.
轮机部已被克林贡人接管
Engineering has been taken over by Klingons
他们切断了生命支持系统
who have cut off life-support systems.
苏鲁先生，去紧急手动控制那里
Mr. Sulu, go to emergency manual control.
尽量保护生命支持电路和辅助动力
Try to protect life-support circuits and auxiliary power.
- 契科夫是对的，舰长  - 斯科提，我很高兴…
- Chekov was right, Captain. - Scotty, I'm glad...
我们应该把那些毛脸的暴徒留在传送器里
We should have left those fuzz-faced goons in the transporter.
- 那是他们该待的地方  - 斯科提？
- That's where they belong. - Scotty?
不存在的地方！
Non-existence!
现在他们可以研究企业号，学习我们的技术
Now they can study the Enterprise, add our technology to theirs,
打破实力平衡，你危害了联邦！
change the balance of power. You've jeopardized the Federation!
- 别紧张  - 把你的瓦肯手拿开！
- Take it easy. - Keep your Vulcan hands off me!
不要碰我，你的感情可能会受到伤害
Just keep away. Your feelings might be hurt,
你这个绿血的杂种！
you green-blooded half-breed!
我能说我并不完全享受与人类共事
May I say that I have not thoroughly enjoyed serving with humans.
我发现他们不合逻辑和愚蠢的情绪总是令人恼火
I find their illogic and foolish emotions a constant irritant.
然后你滚出去，怪胎！
Then transfer out, freak!
先生们！
Gentlemen!
史波克，斯科提，史波克
Spock. Scotty. Spock.
史波克！
Spock!
停下来！你这个半人…
Stop it! You half-human...
我们在说什么？我们在对彼此做什么？
What are we saying? What are we doing to each other?
真有趣，压力…的结果？
Fascinating. The result of... stress?
我们之前一直处于压力之下
We've been under stress before.
它从来不会让我们互相扼住对方的喉咙
It's never set us at each other's throats.
- 这是战争  - 没有战争！
- This is war. - There isn't any war!
还是说有？
Or is there?
我们是否忘记了如何保卫自己？
Have we forgotten how to defend ourselves?
我们怎么了？
What's happening to us?
我们被训练去思考战争以外的其他方面
We've been trained to think in other terms than war.
我们被训练与战争的起因斗争，如果必要的话
We've been trained to fight its causes, if necessary.
那为什么我们表现得像一群野蛮人？
Then why are we behaving like a group of savages?
看着我
Look at me.
这艘船上有两股力量
Two forces aboard this ship,
他们装备得相当
each of them equally armed.
为我们安排了一场战争吗？
Has a war been staged for us?
有武器
Complete with weapons,
和意识形态和爱国鼓声？
and ideology and patriotic drum-beating?
甚至…
Even...
史波克
Spock.
甚至…种族仇恨？
Even... race hatred?
事件似乎旨在放大人类与克林贡人之间的
Events seem to be directed toward magnification of the basic hostilities
基本敌对行动
between humans and Klingons.
显然，我们战斗是被设计好的
Apparently, it is by design that we fight.
- 我们似乎是棋子  - 但这是什么游戏？
- We seem to be pawns. - But what's the game?
谁的游戏？规则是什么？
And whose? And what are the rules?
最紧迫的是我们立即定位外星实体
It is most urgent that we locate the alien entity immediately,
确定其动机并停止其活动
determine its motives and halt its activities.
没有传感器？没有电？这东西可以去任何地方！
Without sensors? All our power down? This thing could go anywhere!
是的
Yes.
- 苏鲁先生，报告  - 不好
- Mr. Sulu, report. - No good.
电路在，但系统没有响应
Circuits are in but systems aren't responding.
我们得到了一些东西
We're getting something.
是的，舰长，电力和生命支持恢复了
Aye, Captain. Power and life-support restored.
- 遥控器在待机状态  - 干得好
- Remotes on standby. - Good work.
但是，舰长，不是我干的，一切都是自己发生的
But, Captain, I didn't do it. Everything just came on by itself.
他们的生命支持系统已经恢复
Their life-support systems have resumed.
- 传感器可能正在运行  - 开始扫描，让我们找到那个外星人
- Sensors may be operating. - Start scanning. Let's find that alien.
- 保持稳定  - 使它们不稳定
- Holding steady. - Cause them to be unsteady.
他们似乎是从另一个位置控制的
They appear to be controlled from another location.
也无法影响返回我们帝国的飞船航线
Also unable to effect ship's course for return to our empire.
柯克的伎俩之一
One of Kirk's tricks.
他能绕过电路吗？
Could he bypass a circuit?
是什么力量支持着我们的战斗，却不让我们获胜？
What power is it that supports our battle yet starves our victory?
力量
Power.
在他们的主要生命支持耦接头处中断它。在哪里？
Interrupt it at their main life-support couplings. Where?
6号甲板
Number 6 deck.
来
Come.
在轮机室检测到外星人，3号反应堆附近
Alien detected in the engineering section, near reactor number 3.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你还没有死
You don't die... yet.
你不是人类，但你很漂亮
You're not human, but you're very beautiful.
很…漂亮
Very... beautiful.
[喘气声]
[GASPS]
契科夫！
Chekov!
吉姆，他没有责任
Jim. He's not responsible.
我做了什么？
What have I done?
船上的一个外星实体迫使我们战斗，我们不想
An alien entity aboard the ship is forcing us to fight. We don't want to.
我们不知道它的动机，我们正试图找出答案，你必须帮助我们
We don't know its motive. We're trying to find out. You must help us.
带我去见康，我只要求暂时休战
Take me to Kang. A temporary truce is all I ask.
史波克，带上她
Spock, take her.
契科夫
Chekov.
这是为我们准备的吗？从这里开始？
Is this what's in store for us? From here on in?
暴力？仇恨？
Violence? Hatred?
脑电波显示偏执狂躁症，发生了什么？
Brain waves show paranoid mania. What happened?
他失去了控制，我也是
He lost control. So did I.
我们正在成为野兽战士
We're becoming animal warriors.
- 我们走吧，史波克  - 勤务兵
- Let's go, Spock. - Orderly.
吉姆…
Jim...
约翰逊的伤几乎痊愈了，和其他人一样
Johnson's wound is almost healed. Same with the others.
重要器官的刀伤，巨大的创伤
Sword wounds in vital organs, massive trauma.
- 正在以惊人的速度愈合  - 实体似乎希望我们活着
- All healing at a fantastic rate. - It appears the entity wants us alive.
为什么？那样我们可以不挺战斗
Why? So we can fight and fight
并继续回来，就像一些血腥的竞技场一样？
and keep coming back for more like some bloody coliseum?
- 下一步是什么？人群的欢呼？  - 也许我们的心理
- What's next? The roar of crowds? - Perhaps our psychologies
和战斗能力正在受到一个外星人的考验
and combat capabilities are being tested
他设计了这两种能力
by an alien with designs on both powers.
如果我们是棋子，那么你看到的是一颗极度后悔的
If we are pawns, you're looking at one who's extremely sorry.
我理解，我也感受到了短暂而澎湃种族偏见
I understand. I too felt a brief surge of racial bigotry.
非常令人不悦
Most distasteful.
让我们找到外星人
Let's find the alien.
你和我们一起来
You come with us.
也许我们可以向你证明它存在
Maybe we can prove to you that it exists.
- 它是什么？  - 完全不清楚
- What is it? - Totally unfamiliar.
你想要什么？
What is it you want?
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
报到，长官
Reporting for duty, sir.
- 报到？麦考伊让你走的吗？  - 我让自己走的
- Duty? Did McCoy release you? - I released myself.
- 那就回医务室  - 我很健康，准备好行动了
- Then get back to Sickbay. - I'm fit and ready for action.
克林贡人差点把我弄进去
The Klingons almost did me in.
- 我命令你…- 我有我的命令
- I order you... - I've got my orders.
- 杀了克林贡人，不是他们就是我们  - 约翰逊！
- Kill the Klingons. It's them or us. - Johnson!
真有趣
Fascinating.
在约翰逊的情绪爆发期间，他的仇恨和对复仇的欲望
During Johnson's emotional outburst, his hatred and lust for vengeance,
外星人的生命能量水平增加了。
the alien's life energy level increased.
当他失去知觉时，外星人失去了能量
When he became unconscious, the alien lost energy.
靠别人的情绪生存？
It subsists on the emotions of others?
这一点似乎被敌意
This one appears to be strengthened
和暴力意图的精神辐射所加强
by mental radiations of hostility, violent intentions.
它存在于他人的仇恨中
It exists on the hate of others.
简而言之，它起到了催化剂的作用
To put it simply. And it has acted as a catalyst,
创造这种情况，以满足这种需要
creating this situation, in order to satisfy that need.
它汇集了敌对势力，提供了粗陋的手段
It has brought together opposing forces, provided crude instruments,
努力促进最暴力的冲突模式
in an effort to promote the most violent mode of conflict.
并保持数量和资源平衡
And kept numbers and resources balanced,
以便它可以维持一种持续的暴力状态
so that it can maintain a constant state of violence.
它一定有弱点，我们必须摆脱它
It's got to have a vulnerable area. We've got to get rid of it.
然后，必须消除船上的所有敌对态度
Then all hostile attitudes on board must be eliminated.
- 战斗必须很快结束  - 否则我们是一艘注定要失败的船
- The fighting must end. And soon. - Or we're a doomed ship,
永远在星系之间旅行，充满了杀戮
traveling forever between galaxies, filled with bloodlust,
永恒的战争
eternal warfare.
康必须要听，我们必须共享我们的知识
Kang has got to listen. We've got to pool our knowledge.
并摆脱这件事
And get rid of this thing.
康
Kang.
康，我是柯克舰长
Kang, this is Captain Kirk.
你听到了吗？
Do you read me?
指挥官，这是个伎俩！
Commander, it's a trick!
康
Kang.
- 他不会回答  - 外星人正在影响他的思想
- He won't answer. - The alien is affecting his mind.
很快，它就会强大到我们无人能抵抗它
Soon, it will become so powerful that none of us will be able to resist it.
斯科提，长官，二锂晶体正在恶化，我们无法阻止
Scotty, sir. The dilithium crystals are deteriorating. We can't stop it.
时间因数？
Time factor?
12分钟内，我们将失去引擎动力
In 12 minutes, we'll be without engine power.
好吧，尽你所能，通话完毕
Well, do whatever you can. Kirk out.
所以我们在太空中漂流
And so we drift in space,
船上只有仇恨和杀戮
with only hatred and bloodshed aboard.
现在，你相信了吗？
Now, do you believe?
柯克：舰长日志，星历…大决战
KIRK: Captain's log, stardate... Armageddon.
我们必须找到一种方法来击败
We must find a way to defeat the alien force of hate
接管企业号的外星仇恨力量，现在停止战争
that has taken over the Enterprise, stop the war now,
或在无用，血腥的暴力中度过永恒
or spend eternity in futile, bloody violence.
没变化，二锂晶体正在放电
No change. The dilithium crystals are discharging.
我们对此无能为力
There's nothing we can do about it.
如果我能和康谈谈
If I could talk to Kang,
切断克林贡防线，在为时已晚之前实现和平
cut through the Klingon lines, make peace before it's too late.
能量还能撑9分53秒
We have nine minutes, 53 seconds to power zero.
当然，还有一个合乎逻辑的选择
There is of course, a logical alternative.
康的妻子是我们的囚犯
Kang's wife is our prisoner.
- 也许是一种威胁…  - 是的！
- Perhaps a threat... - Aye!
这是克林贡人会理解的事情
That's something the Klingons would understand.
康！
Kang!
这是柯克舰长，我知道你能听到我的声音，所以不要挂断
This is Captain Kirk. I know you can hear me so don't cut me off.
我们有玛拉，你的妻子
We have Mara, your wife.
我们现在商量休战，否则她会死，回复
We talk truce now, or she dies. Reply.
她还有五秒钟的生命
She has five seconds to live.
回复
Reply.
她是战争的受害者，舰长
She is a victim of war, Captain.
她明白
She understands.
他认为我在虚张声势
He called my bluff.
你不会…
You're not going to...
联邦不杀囚犯，那是宣传
The Federation doesn't kill prisoners. That's propaganda.
- 多少时间？  - 8分42秒
- How much time? - Eight minutes, 42 seconds.
- 所以这不是把戏  - 斯科特：是外星人干的
- So this was no trick. - SCOTT: It's the alien that's done this.
我们在它的控制中，我们所有人
We're in its power. All of us.
我们想停止战斗以拯救我们所有人
We wanted to stop the fighting to save us all.
我们一直在战斗，我们必须
We have always fought. We must.
我们是猎人，追踪并获取我们需要的东西
We are hunters, tracking and taking what we need.
克林贡星系中有一些可怜的行星
There are poor planets in the Klingon systems,
如果我们要生存，就必须向外推进
we must push outward if we are to survive.
还有另一种生存方式，相互信任和帮助
There's another way to survive. Mutual trust and help.
我现在就帮你
I will help you now.
- 如何？  - 我带你去见康
- How? - I will take you to Kang.
- 我会帮你说话  - 我不会相信她
- I will add my voice to yours. - I wouldn't trust her.
我们无法及时通过克林贡防御
We can't get through the Klingon defenses in time.
除非…
Unless...
史波克
Spock.
在船内从一个区域传送到另一区域， 可能吗？
Intra-ship beaming from one section to another. It's possible?
由于所涉及的风险，很少有人这样做
It has rarely been done because of the danger involved.
如果运输者在固体物体、甲板或墙壁内实体化…
If the transportee materialized inside a solid object, a deck or a wall...
即使它可以奏效，她也可能将你带入陷阱
Even if it could work, she may be leading you into a trap.
我们都在陷阱中，这是唯一的出路
We're all in a trap. This is the only way out.
- 我们和你一起去  - 不，那将开始最后的战斗
- We'll go with you. - No, that would start the final battle.
我相信她
I believe her.
准备传送机，我们会等待你的信号
Prepare the transporter. We'll wait for your signal.
她不能保证康会停下来听，对吧，史波克先生？
She can't guarantee that Kang will stop to listen. Right, Mr. Spock?
没有人可以保证另一个人的行为
No one can guarantee the actions of another.
您的自动设置已完成
Your automatic setting is laid in.
当传送器通电时，您将有八秒钟的时间到达传送台
When transporter is energized, you will have eight seconds to get to the pads.
我希望你的计算是正确的
I hope your computations are correct.
你将在7.9秒内知道
You will know in 7.9 seconds.
玛拉，你还活着，你给我们带来了战利品
Mara. You're alive and you bring us a prize.
康，等等！他一个人来的，手无寸铁，他必须和你谈谈
Kang wait! He's come alone, unarmed. He must talk to you.
- 勇敢的舰长，关于什么？  - 不！听他说
- Brave captain. What about? - No! Listen to him.
- 我们都处于危险之中  - 玛拉
- We are all in danger. - Mara.
在你开始杀人之前，给我一分钟
Before you start killing, give me one minute.
- 康，不要！  - 他们对你做了什么？
- Kang, don't! - What have they done to you?
你疯了吗？他们对你做了什么？
Are you out of your mind? What have they done to you?
我明白了为什么野兽没有杀了你
I see why the beast did not kill you.
他们没有伤害我，听他说！
They didn't harm me. Listen to him!
停止！请停下来！
Stop! Stop, please!
- 你死了，我们就赢了  - 没有人赢
- With your death, we win. - Nobody wins.
你的手下还有人死了吗？我们不能被杀死
Have any more of your men died? We can't be killed.
船上有外星人，它想让我们活着
There's an alien aboard. It wants us alive.
毫无疑问，在我把你砍成碎片后，你会重新组装起来
No doubt you will reassemble after I've hacked you to bits.
你这个傻瓜
You fool.
听我说！
Look!
听我说，康，在我们的余生中，千百世时间
Look, Kang. For the rest of our lives, a thousand lifetimes,
毫无意义的暴力，战斗
senseless violence, fighting,
而一个外星人完全控制着我们
while an alien has total control over us.
好吧
All right.
在心里，在头上，我不会死去，下次，我会杀了你
In the heart, the head, I won't stay dead. Next time, I'll kill you.
一直持续下去，战争的游戏，卒子对卒子
And it goes on and on, the game of war. Pawn against pawn.
阻止坏人
Stopping the bad guys,
而某个地方，某些人坐在背后大笑
while somewhere, some thing sits back and laughs.
并重新开始
And starts it all over again.
- 让我们扑向它  - 那些憎恨和战斗的人
- Let's jump him. - Those who hate and fight
一定要自己停下来，否则，它不会停止
must stop themselves, otherwise, it is not stopped.
康，我是你的妻子
Kang, I am your wife.
我是克林贡人，我会为他们撒谎吗？
I'm a Klingon. Would I lie for them?
听柯克说，他说的是实话
Listen to Kirk. He is telling the truth.
做一个棋子，做一个玩具，做一个从不质疑命令的好士兵
Be a pawn, be a toy, a good soldier who never questions orders.
- 克林贡人为了自己的目的而杀人  - 所有的战斗都必须结束
- Klingons kill for their own purposes. - All fighting must end,
在我们的二锂晶体消失之前削弱外星人
to weaken the alien before our dilithium crystals are gone.
- 乌乎拉  - 是的，舰长
- Uhura. - Yes, Captain.
- 把我接入全船对讲机  - 是的，长官
- Put me on ship-wide intercom. - Aye, sir.
准备好了，舰长
Ready, Captain.
这是柯克舰长
This is Captain Kirk.
下令休战，战斗结束了
A truce is ordered. The fighting is over.
放下你的武器
Lay down your weapons.
这是康
This is Kang.
停止敌对行动，解除武装
Cease hostilities. Disarm.
暴力的停止削弱了它
The cessation of violence has weakened it.
我认为好心情可能是一种有效的武器
I suggest that good spirits might make an effective weapon.
滚出我的船
Get off my ship.
你是一只死鸭子了，我们知道你
You're a dead duck, we know about you,
我们不想玩了
and we don't want to play.
也许周围还有其他像你一样的东西
Maybe there are others like you around,
也许你造成了很多痛苦，很多历史，但一切都结束了
maybe you've caused a lot of suffering, a lot of history, but that's all over.
我们现在会保持警惕，我们会为你做好准备，所以出去吧！
We'll be on guard now, we'll be ready for you, so ship out!
- 来吧，拉它！  - 是的，已经出去了！
- Come on, haul it! - Yeah, out already!
出去！我们无需催促就憎恨人类
Out! We need no urging to hate humans.
但就目前而言，只有傻瓜才会在着火的房子里战斗，出去！
But for the present, only a fool fights in a burning house. Out!